export const sections = {
	process: {
		title: 'Editorial Process',
		topics: [
			{
				title: 'Curriculum Evaluation',
				questions: [
					{
						question: 'Why must my curriculum be evaluated',
						answer: 'All types of curricula must be evaluated for quality assurance. An evaluation is needed to ensure that ' +
                        'all curricula released on CLARK contain no issues with any of the characteristics mentioned above. Since all ' +
                        'released curricula fall under Creative Commons, it is necessary to ensure all content is of the best quality ' +
                        'possible.'
					},
					{
						question: 'How is the curriculum evaluated?',
						answer: 'All curriculum goes through an evaluation process that reviews a curriculum\'s required ' +
                        'characteristics. These characteristics act as the evaluated criteria for the editorial process: ' +
                        '\n-Proper contributor attribution. \n-Writing style, grammar, punctuation, and capitalization. ' +
                        '\n-Accessibility under WCAG 2.1 AA standards. \n-If the curriculum\'s content can be understood ' +
                        'by its intended audience. \n-Consistent formatting of curriculum content. \n-Relevant learning outcomes are ' +
                        'present. Some curricula will have conditional evaluations (if provided) over these characteristics: ' +
                        '\n-Documentation of a provided syllabus. \n-The curriculum is part of a learning object hierarchy with proper ' +
                        'parent-child relationships. \n-Provided assessment questions do not include solutions (CLARK is a public ' +
                        'website that all types of audiences can access).'
					},
					{
						question: 'The Editorial Review Process',
						answer: 'The editorial review process is a multi-week evaluation done by CLARK\'s editorial team to review ' +
                        'submitted curricula. Curricula are reviewed and documented for any potential issues that require fixes. ' +
                        'The editorial team will fix any minor problems such as typos, grammar, punctuation, formatting, and ' +
                        'alternative text for imagery during the process. The editorial team will also provide any needed ' +
                        'documentation to the author of major problems that require fixes from the author\'s side, such as missing ' +
                        'files and incomplete curricula. The editorial team will never majorly alter content, such as removing ' +
                        'text, files, or imagery. Any changes made by the editorial team are quality of life changes to provide ' +
                        'the authors less needed work.'
					},
					{
						question: 'Learning Object  Statuses',
						answer: 'Every curriculum submitted becomes a learning object and will have a designated status in the ' +
                        'editorial review process. Statuses allow an author to track where a learning object is currently in ' +
                        'the process or if it was already released. \n-A learning object can have the following statuses: ' +
                        '\n-Draft Learning Objects: Unsubmitted learning objects. \n-Waiting: Submitted learning objects ' +
                        'that have yet to be reviewed. \n-Review: Learning objects that are currently being reviewed. ' +
                        '\n-Accepted Minor Changes: Learning objects that could be accepted after the author applies minor changes. ' +
                        '\n-Accepted Major Changes: Learning objects that could be accepted after the author applies major changes. ' +
                        '\n-Proofing: Learning objects that are being prepped for release with small quality of life changes made ' +
                        'by the editorial team. \n-Released: Learning objects that have been approved and are now publicly ' +
                        'available on CLARK. \n-Rejected: Learning objects that are deemed not releasable on CLARK.'
					},
					{
						question: 'How Long is the Editorial Review Process?',
						answer: 'Depending on the learning object size and quantity, the editorial review process ' +
                        'is estimated to take two to four weeks. Throughout the process, the author is communicated ' +
                        'with for any needed feedback of a submitted object. '
					}
				],
            },
            {
				title: 'The Curriculum Development Lifecycle',
				questions:[
					{
						question: 'What is the Curriculum Development Lifecycle?',
						answer: 'The curriculum development lifecycle is the multi-stage sequence of any submitted learning object. ' +
                        'Each stage is based on a learning object status and the routes a learning object can take. The curriculum ' +
                        'development lifecycle aims to provide a physical representation of a learning object on CLARK. The diagram ' +
                        'below demonstrates how the lifecycle operates.'
                        //picture
					},
					{
						question: 'Why was my learning object rejected?',
						answer: 'A learning object was rejected as it did not meet the criteria requirements found under the "How ' +
                        'Curriculum is Evaluated" above. The author is provided specific reasoning for rejection and encouraged to' +
                        'resubmit later on with an improved or new learning object.'
					},
					{
						question: 'What is the difference between acceptance minor and acceptance major?',
						answer: 'Both statuses require action from the author as there are changes that the editorial team cannot ' +
                        'make. The main differences in statuses are provided below: \n-Accepted Major \n-A learning object is missing ' +
                        'files. \n-A learning object video does not have captioning. \n-A learning object lacks proper contributor ' +
                        'attribution. \n-A learning object file has an incomplete paragraph or section. \n-A learning object contains ' +
                        'some outdated curriculum. \n-Accepted Minor \n-A learning object contains assessment solutions. \n-A learning ' +
                        'object has a color contrast issue. \n-A learning object was submitted to the wrong collection. \n-A learning ' +
                        'object is under the wrong learning object length.'
					},
					{
						question: 'What is the difference for an object to be in \'Review\' and \'Proofing\'?',
						answer: 'A learning object going through a review status is only being evaluated and documented on any ' +
                        'potential problems. On the other hand, a learning object going through a proofing status has small fixes ' +
                        'applied to minor issues such as typos, grammar, punctuation, formatting, and alternative text for imagery. ' +
                        'Typically, a proofing status is near the end of the review lifecycle, while a review status is at the start.'
					},
					{
						question: 'Can I make changes to my Learning Object after it was accepted?',
						answer: 'Yes, an author can make any changes to their released learning object through revisions. A revision ' +
                        'allows an author to see and edit their current learning object version in the learning object builder. The ' +
                        'author is free to add, replace, and remove varying content. When an author finishes a revision, the ' +
                        'learning object is resubmitted and goes through the curriculum development lifecycle.'
					}
                ]
            }
        ]
    }
};
